<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: IUI | Joseph Chee Chang]]></title>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/blog/categories/iui/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-11-26T07:46:20-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://josephcc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Joseph Chee Chang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[josephcc@cmu.edu]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[SearchLens]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/IUI-searchlens/"/>
    <updated>2019-03-17T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/IUI-searchlens</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Whether figuring out where to eat in an unfamiliar city or deciding which
apartment to live in, reviews and forum posts are often a significant factor in
online decision making. However, making sense of these rich repositories of
diverse opinions can be prohibitively effortful, searchers need to sift through
a large number of reviews to characterize each item based on aspects that they
care about. We introduce a novel system, SearchLens, where searchers build up a
collection of composable and reusable "Lenses" that reflect their different
latent interests. Also, the Lenses allowed the system to generate personalized
interfaces with visual explanations that promote transparency and enable
in-depth exploration.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Whether figuring out where to eat in an unfamiliar city or deciding which
apartment to live in, consumer generated data (i.e. reviews and forum posts)
are often an important influence in online decision making. To make sense of
these rich repositories of diverse opinions, searchers need to sift through a
large number of reviews to characterize each item based on aspects that they
care about. We introduce a novel system, SearchLens, where searchers build up a
collection of "Lenses" that reflect their different latent interests, and
compose the Lenses to find relevant items across different contexts. Based on
the Lenses, SearchLens generates personalized interfaces with visual
explanations that promotes transparency and enables deeper exploration. While
prior work found searchers may not wish to put in effort specifying their goals
without immediate and sufficient benefits, results from a controlled lab study
suggest that our approach incentivized participants to express their interests
more richly than in a baseline condition, and a field study showed that
participants found benefits in SearchLens while conducting their own tasks.</p>

<h2>Video Figure</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dXcTtHMa2DQ?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/searchlens.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'SearchLens', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=3302321" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'SearchLens', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>SearchLens: Composing and Capturing Complex User Interests for Exploratory Search.
Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, Adam Perer, Aniket Kittur.
In Proceedings of the 2019 ACM 24th Annual Meeting of the Intelligent User Interfaces: IUI 2019.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{chang2019searchlens,
  title={SearchLens: Composing and Capturing Complex User Interests for Exploratory Search},
  author={Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan, and Perer, Adam and Kittur, Aniket},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2019 ACM 24th Annual Meeting of the Intelligent User Interfaces},
  series = {IUI'19},
  year={2019}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
