<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: HCI | Joseph Chee Chang]]></title>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/blog/categories/hci/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2023-02-03T15:30:50-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://josephcc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Joseph Chee Chang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[josephc->allenai*org]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[CiteSee]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-citesee/"/>
    <updated>2023-04-23T08:10:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-citesee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> CiteSee provides a personalized paper reading experience by visually
 augmenting inline citations based on their connections to the current user
 based on their reading history, paper library, and publication records.
 During literature review sessions, CiteSee allows users to prioritize their
 exploration to focus first on inline citations most relevant to their recent
 readings. It also highlights inline citations to familiar papers, allowing
 users to keep track of their exploration and better contexturalize the current
 paper. Lab and field studies showed CiteSee can improve better paper discovery
 via inline citations, and allowed participants to have better situational
 awareness when conducting real-world literature reviews.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>When reading a scholarly article, inline citations help researchers
contextualize the current article and discover relevant prior work. However, it
can be challenging to prioritize and make sense of the hundreds of citations
encountered during literature reviews. This paper introduces CiteSee, a paper
reading tool that leverages a user's publishing, reading, and saving activities
to provide personalized visual augmentations and context around citations.
First, CiteSee connects the current paper to familiar contexts by surfacing
known citations a user had cited or opened. Second, CiteSee helps users
prioritize their exploration by highlighting relevant but unknown citations
based on saving and reading history. We conducted a lab study that suggests
CiteSee is significantly more effective for paper discovery than three
baselines. A field deployment study shows CiteSee helps participants keep
track of their explorations and leads to better situational awareness and
increased paper discovery via inline citation when conducting real-world
literature reviews.</p>

<h2>Presentation (SIGCHI 2023)</h2>

<p>coming soon...</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p>coming soon...</p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Amy X. Zhang, Jonathan Bragg, Andrew Head, Kyle
Lo, Doug Downey, and Daniel S. Weld. 2023.
CiteSee: Augmenting Citations in Scientific Papers with Persistent and Personalized Historical Context.
In Proceedings of the 2023 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing
Systems (CHI ’23), April 23–28, 2023, Hamburg, Germany. ACM, New York,
NY, USA, Article 111, 15 pages. https://doi.org/10.1145/3544548.3580847
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<p>coming soon</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relatedly]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-relatedly/"/>
    <updated>2023-04-23T08:05:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-relatedly</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Scientific breakthroughs often rely upon scholars synthesizing many published
work into broad overviews and rich insights to identify gaps in the current
literature.  However, survey articles require significant time and effort to
synthesize and can quickly become outdated. Researchers in fast-paced
disciplines also rely on the related work section to better understand the
background when reading a paper.  While related work sections also summarizes
multiple prior work, they typically provide partial views of the larger
research domain. Relatedly explore how a system in which users can quickly
explore and read related work sections extracted across many papers can help
scholars gain richer and more comprehensive overviews of fast-paced domains.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Scholars who want to research a scientific topic must take time to read,
extract meaning, and identify connections across many papers. As scientific
literature grows, this becomes increasingly challenging. Meanwhile, authors
summarize prior research in papers' related work sections, though this is
scoped to support a single paper. A formative study found that while reading
multiple related work paragraphs helps overview a topic, it is hard to navigate
overlapping and diverging references and research foci.  In this work, we
design a system, Relatedly, that scaffolds exploring and reading multiple
related work paragraphs on a topic, with features including dynamic re-ranking
and highlighting to spotlight unexplored dissimilar information, auto-generated
descriptive paragraph headings, and low-lighting of redundant information. From
a within-subjects user study (n=15), we found that scholars generate more
coherent, insightful, and comprehensive topic outlines using Relatedly compared
to a baseline paper list.</p>

<h2>Presentation (SIGCHI 2023)</h2>

<p>coming soon...</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p>coming soon...</p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Srishti Palani, Aakanksha Naik, Doug Downey, Amy X. Zhang, Jonathan
Bragg, and Joseph Chee Chang. 2023. Relatedly: Scaffolding Literature
Reviews with Existing Related Work Sections. In Proceedings of the 2023
CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI ’23), April
23–28, 2023, Hamburg, Germany. ACM, New York, NY, USA, 19 pages.
https://doi.org/10.1145/3544548.3580841
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<p>coming soon</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[ComLittee]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-comlittee/"/>
    <updated>2023-04-23T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-comlittee</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Significant research has been devoted to creating systems that help scholars
discover relevant papers.  While recent approaches have also shown benefits in
highlighting relevant authors to improve paper discovery, these systems do not
capture and utilize users' evolving knowledge of authors.  We introduce
ComLittee, a literature discovery system that supports author-centric
exploration.  ComLittee supports author discovery to curation of a
comittee of authors relevant to a research topic of interests based on existing
paper recommendation systems.  In our evaluation, we demonstrate how ComLittee
leads to a higher efficiency, quality, and novelty in author discovery that
also improves paper discovery.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>In order to help scholars understand and follow a research topic, significant
research has been devoted to creating systems that help scholars discover
relevant papers and authors.  Recent approaches have shown the usefulness of
highlighting relevant authors while scholars engage in paper discovery.
However, these systems do not capture and utilize users' evolving knowledge of
authors.  We reflect on the design space and introduce ComLittee, a literature
discovery system that supports author-centric exploration.  In contrast to
paper-centric interaction in prior systems, ComLittee's author-centric
interaction supports curation of research threads from individual authors,
finding new authors and papers with combined signals from a paper recommender
and the curated authors' authorship graphs, and understanding them in the
context of those signals.  In a within-subjects experiment that compares to an
author-highlighting approach, we demonstrate how ComLittee leads to a higher
efficiency, quality, and novelty in author discovery that also improves paper
discovery.</p>

<h2>Presentation (SIGCHI 2023)</h2>

<p>coming soon...</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p>coming soon...</p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Hyeonsu B. Kang, Nouran Soliman, Matt Latzke, Joseph Chee Chang, and Jonathan
Bragg. 2023. ComLittee: Literature Discovery with Personal Elected Author
Committees. In Proceedings of the 2023 CHI Conference on Human Factors in
Computing Systems (CHI ’23), April 23–28, 2023, Hamburg, Germany. ACM,
New York, NY, USA, 20 pages. https://doi.org/10.1145/3544548.3581371
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<p>coming soon</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threddy]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-Threddy/"/>
    <updated>2022-10-29T07:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-Threddy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Reviewing the literature to understand relevant past work is a critical part of
research. However, as the scientific literature grows the challenges for users
to find and make sense of the many different threads of research grow as well.
In this work we explore a tool integrated into users' reading process that
helps them with leveraging authors' existing summarization of prior research
threads such as in related work sections.  We developed Threddy that supports
efficient extraction and organization of threads along with supporting evidence
as scientists read research articles. The system then recommends further
relevant articles based on user-created threads.  Our lab study showed that
Threddy helps scientists to follow and curate research threads without breaking
out of their flow of reading, collect relevant papers and clips, and discover
interesting new articles to further grow threads.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Reviewing the literature to understand relevant threads of past work is a
critical part of research and vehicle for learning. However, as the scientific
literature grows the challenges for users to find and make sense of the many
different threads of research grow as well. Previous work has helped scholars
to find and group papers with citation information or textual similarity using
standalone tools or overview visualizations. Instead, in this work we explore a
tool integrated into users' reading process that helps them with leveraging
authors' existing summarization of threads, typically in introduction or
related work sections, in order to situate their own work's contributions. To
explore this we developed a prototype that supports efficient extraction and
organization of threads along with supporting evidence as scientists read
research articles. The system then recommends further relevant articles based
on user-created threads. We evaluate the system in a lab study and find that it
helps scientists to follow and curate research threads without breaking out of
their flow of reading, collect relevant papers and clips, and discover
interesting new articles to further grow threads.</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/threddy.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Threddy', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2208.03455" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Threddy', 'arXiv']);"  role="button">arXiv</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Hyeonsu B. Kang, Joseph Chee Chang, Yongsung Kim, Aniket Kittur
"Threddy: An Interactive System for Personalized Thread-based Exploration and Organization of Scientific Literature"
In Proceedings of the 35th ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium: UIST 2022.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{kang2022threddy,
 title={Threddy: An Interactive System for Personalized Thread-based Exploration and Organization of Scientific Literature},
 author={Kang, Hyeonsu B and Chang, Joseph Chee and Kim, Yongsung and Kittur, Aniket},
 booktitle = {},
 series = {UIST '22},
 year = {2022},
 location = {Bend, OR, USA},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuse]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-Fuse/"/>
    <updated>2022-10-29T06:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-Fuse</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While people can fluidly collect, make sense of  and organize information
across many online sources in their minds to make informed decisions, the
amount of online information can be overwhelming and exceed people's working
memory.  We introduce Fuse, a browser extension that combined low-cost
collection with lightweight organization of web content in a compact card-based
sidebar.  Fuse helps users simultaneously extract key web content and structure
it in a lightweight and visual way.  A 22-month public deployment and
interviews provide longitudinal insights into the collecting, externalization
and  structuring behaviors of real-world users conducting information foraging
tasks.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>People spend a significant amount of time trying to make sense of the internet,
collecting content from a variety of sources and organizing it to make
decisions and achieve their goals. While humans are able to fluidly iterate on
collecting and organizing information in their minds, existing tools and
approaches introduce significant friction into the process. We introduce Fuse,
a browser extension that externalizes users' working memory by combining
low-cost collection with lightweight organization of content in a compact
card-based sidebar that is always available. Fuse helps users simultaneously
extract key web content and structure it in a lightweight and visual way. We
discuss how these affordances help users externalize more of their mental model
into the system (e.g., saving, annotating, and structuring items) and support
fast reviewing and resumption of task contexts. Our 22-month public deployment
and follow-up interviews provide longitudinal insights into the structuring
behaviors of real-world users conducting information foraging tasks.</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/fuse.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Fuse', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2208.14861" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Fuse', 'arXiv']);"  role="button">arXiv</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Kuznetsov, Andrew, Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, Napol Rachatasumrit, Bradley Breneisen, Julina Coupland, and Aniket Kittur.
"Fuse: In-Situ Sensemaking Support in the Browser."
In Proceedings of the 35th ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium: UIST 2022.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{kuznetsov2022fuse,
 title={Fuse: In-Situ Sensemaking Support in the Browser},
 author={Kuznetsov, Andrew and Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan and Rachatasumrit, Napol and Breneisen, Bradley and Coupland, Julina and Kittur, Aniket},
 booktitle = {},
 series = {UIST '22},
 year = {2022},
 location = {Bend, OR, USA},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
