<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: UIST | Joseph Chee Chang]]></title>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/blog/categories/uist/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-11-26T08:00:28-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://josephcc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Joseph Chee Chang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[josephcc@cmu.edu]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesh]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-mesh/"/>
    <updated>2020-10-20T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-mesh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Consumers can choose from many different products and base their decisions on
the tens of thousands of online evidence about each of their options.  However,
to synthesize this information into confident decisions can incur high
interaction and cognitive costs. Online information is scattered across
different sources, and evidence such as reviews can be subjective and
conflicting, requiring users to interpret them under their personal context. We
introduce Mesh, which scaffolds users in iteratively building up a better
understanding of both their choices by evaluating evidence gathered across
sources. Lab and field deployment studies found that Mesh significantly reduces
the costs of gathering and evaluating evidence and scaffolds decision-making
through personalized criteria enabling users to gain deeper insights from data
to make confident purchase decisions.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>While there is an enormous amount of information online for making decisions
such as choosing a product, restaurant, or school, it can be costly for users
to synthesize that information into confident decisions. Information for users'
many different criteria needs to be gathered from many different sources into a
structure where they can be compared and contrasted. The usefulness of each
criterion for differentiating potential options can be opaque to users, and
evidence such as reviews may be subjective and conflicting, requiring users to
interpret each under their personal context. We introduce Mesh, which
scaffolds users in iteratively building up a better understanding of both their
criteria and options by evaluating evidence gathered across sources in the
context of consumer decision making. Mesh bridges the gap between decision
support systems that typically have rigid structures and the fluid and dynamic
process of exploratory search, changing the cost structure to provide
increasing payoffs with greater user investment. Our lab and field deployment
studies found evidence that Mesh significantly reduces the costs of
gathering and evaluating evidence and scaffolds decision-making through
personalized criteria enabling users to gain deeper insights from data.</p>

<h2>Video Figure</h2>

<h4>5-minute virtual conference presentation</h4>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LNASh9rq9-I?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h4>3-minute video abstract</h4>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NqriHlTfVhU?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/mesh.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Mesh', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3379337.3415865" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Mesh', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, Aniket Kittur.
Mesh: Scaffolding Comparison Tables for Online Decision Making.
In Proceedings of the 33rd ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium: UIST 2020.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{chang2020mesh,
  title={Mesh: Scaffolding Comparison Tables for Online Decision Making},
  author={Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan, and Kittur, Aniket},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 33rd ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium},
  series = {UIST'20},
  year={2020}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intentionally Uncertain Input]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-highlight/"/>
    <updated>2016-10-16T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-highlight</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Highlighting can be mentally taxing for learners who are often unsure about how
much information they needed to include.  We introduce the idea of
intentionally uncertain input in the context of highlighting on mobile devices.
We present a system that uses force touch and fuzzy bounding boxes to support
saving information while users are uncertain about where to highlight.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Patients researching medical diagnoses, scientist exploring new fields of
literature, and students learning about new domains are all faced with the
challenge of capturing information they find for later use. However, saving
information is challenging on mobile devices, where the small screen and font
sizes combined with the inaccuracy of finger based touch screens makes it time
consuming and stressful for people to select and save text for future use.
Furthermore, beyond the challenge of simply selecting a region of bounded text
on a mobile device, in many learning and data exploration tasks the boundaries
of what text may be relevant and useful later are themselves uncertain for the
user. In contrast to previous approaches which focused on speeding up the
selection process by making the identification of hard boundaries faster, we
introduce the idea of intentionally supporting uncertain input in the context
of saving information during complex reading and information exploration. We
embody this idea in a system that uses force touch and fuzzy bounding boxes
along with posthoc expandable context to support identifying and saving
information in an intentionally uncertain way on mobile devices. In a two part
user study we find that this approach reduced selection time and was preferred
by participants over the default system text selection method.</p>

<h2>Presentation (UIST 2016)</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HPG6NWRTGvY?list=PLqhXYFYmZ-VcUPus2QYpAZdFmw5w6seVR" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Demo Video</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Rj_0GFeUQjg?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/mobile-highlighting.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Highlight', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2984538" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Highlight', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, and Aniket Kittur. 2016.
Supporting Mobile Sensemaking Through Intentionally Uncertain Highlighting.
In Proceedings of the 29th Annual Symposium on User Interface Software and Technology (UIST '16).
ACM, New York, NY, USA, 61-68. DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.1145/2984511.2984538
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Chang:2016:SMS:2984511.2984538,
 author = {Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan and Kittur, Aniket},
 title = {Supporting Mobile Sensemaking Through Intentionally Uncertain Highlighting},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 29th Annual Symposium on User Interface Software and Technology},
 series = {UIST '16},
 year = {2016},
 isbn = {978-1-4503-4189-9},
 location = {Tokyo, Japan},
 pages = {61--68},
 numpages = {8},
 url = {http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/2984511.2984538},
 doi = {10.1145/2984511.2984538},
 acmid = {2984538},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA},
 keywords = {annotation, capture, copy-paste, highlighting., information, saving, sensemaking},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
