<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Information Extraction | Joseph Chee Chang]]></title>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/blog/categories/information-extraction/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2023-04-04T02:03:46-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://josephcc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Joseph Chee Chang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[josephc->allenai*org]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[TermMine]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/ACL-termmine/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/ACL-termmine</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>TermMine is an information extraction system that can automatically mine
translation pairs of terms from the web. We used a small set of terms and
translations to gather mixed-code text from the web to train a CRF model that
can identify translation pairs at run-time.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>In this paper, we present a new method for learning to finding translations and
transliterations on the Web for a given term. The approach involves using a
small set of terms and translations to obtain mixed-code snippets from a search
engine, and automatically annotating the snippets with tags and features for
training a conditional random field model. At run-time, the model is used to
extracting translation candidates for a given term. Preliminary experiments and
evaluation show our method cleanly combining various features, resulting in a
system that outperforms previous work.</p>

<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'TermMine', 'PDF']);"  href="http://www.aclweb.org/anthology/P12-2026" role="button">ACLWeb Hosted PDF</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'TermMine', 'ACM']);"  href="http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2390665.2390698" role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Z. Chang, Jason S. Chang, and Jyh-Shing Roger Jang. 2012.
Learning to find translations and transliterations on the web.
In Proceedings of the 50th Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics.
Association for Computational Linguistics, Stroudsburg, PA, USA, 130-134.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Chang:2012:LFT:2390665.2390698,
 author = {Chang, Joseph Z. and Chang, Jason S. and Jang, Jyh-Shing Roger},
 title = {Learning to Find Translations and Transliterations on the Web},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 50th Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics},
 series = {ACL '12},
 year = {2012},
 location = {Jeju Island, Korea},
 pages = {130--134},
 numpages = {5},
 url = {http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2390665.2390698},
 acmid = {2390698},
 publisher = {Association for Computational Linguistics},
 address = {Stroudsburg, PA, USA},
} 
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[WikiSense]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/wikisense/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-03T08:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/wikisense</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We introduced a method for classifying named-entities into broad semantic
categories in WordNet. We extracted rich features from Wikipedia, allowing us
to classify named-entities with high precision and coverage. The result is a
large scale named-entity semantic database with 1.2 million entries and over
95% accuracy, covering 80% of all named-entities found on Wikipedia.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>In this paper, we introduce a minimally supervised method for learning to
classify named-entity titles in a given encyclopedia into broad semantic
categories in an existing ontology. Our main idea involves using overlapping
entries in the encyclopedia and ontology and a small set of 30 handed tagged
parenthetic explanations to automatically generate the training data. The
proposed method involves automatically recognizing whether a title is a named
entity, automatically generating two sets of training data, and automatically
building a classification model for training a classification model based on
textual and non-textual features. We present WikiSense, an implementation of
the proposed method for extending the named entity coverage of WordNet by sense
tagging Wikipedia titles. Experimental results show WikiSense achieves accuracy
of over 95% and near 80% applicability for all NE titles in Wikipedia.
WikiSense cleanly produces over 1.2 million of NEs tagged with broad
categories, based on the lexicographers’ files of WordNet, effectively
extending WordNet to form a very large scale semantic category, a potentially
useful resource for many natural language related tasks.</p>

<h2>Demo</h2>

<pre><code>WikiID    Supersense     PE          NE                                   Note
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
11983070  person         None        Johnny Cash                          singer
203407    person         None        Celine Dion                          singer
2773076   group          None        Guns N' Roses                        band

945778    location       None        Hsinchu Science and Industrial Park
951038    location       None        Linbian, Pingtung                    name of city

19299838  communication  None        Cape No. 7                           movie
543675    person         None        Jay Chou                             singer

1374293   group          None        National Chung Hsing University
2012972   group          None        Yuan Ze University

412376    animal         butterfly   Queen                                namd of speices
42010     group          band        Queen                                name of band
10309519  communication  magazine    Queen                                name of maagazine
559004    artifcact      automobile  Queen                                car model name
718750    communication  album       Queen                                music album
570546    person         Snow White  Queen                                fictional character
130425    artifcact      TTC         Queen                                subway station
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
</code></pre>

<p>PE, parenthetic explanations, see <a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Disambiguation'>Wikipedia guideline on resolving ambiguous titles</a>.</p>

<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'WikiSense', 'PDF']);" href="http://www.aclweb.org/anthology/Y09-1009" role="button">ACLWeb Hosted PDF</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'WikiSense', 'Dataset']);" href="http://moon.cse.yzu.edu.tw/WikiSense/release.tbz2" role="button">Dataset Download</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Chang, J., Tsai, R. T.-H., &amp; Chang, J. S. (2009).
WikiSense: Supersense Tagging of Wikipedia Named Entities Based WordNet.
In Proceedings of the 23rd Pacific Asia Conference on Language, Information and Computation (PACLIC) (72–81)
Hong Kong, China. 
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Chang-EtAl:2009:PACLIC2009,
  author = {Chang, Joseph and Tsai, Richard Tzong-Han and Chang, Jason S.},
  title = {WikiSense: Supersense Tagging of Wikipedia Named Entities Based WordNet},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 23rd Pacific Asia Conference on Language, Information and Computation (PACLIC)},
  year = {2009},
  month = {dec},
  address = {Hong Kong, China},
  pages = {72--81},
  url = {http://www.aclweb.org/anthology/Y09-1009}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
