<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Crowdsourcing | Joseph Chee Chang]]></title>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/blog/categories/crowdsourcing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2022-10-28T15:15:08-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://josephcc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Joseph Chee Chang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[josephc->allenai*org]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solvent]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CSCW-solvent/"/>
    <updated>2018-11-03T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CSCW-solvent</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Analogies in distant domains often lead to scientific discoveries. However, it
can be prohibitively difficult for researchers to find useful analogies from
unfamiliar domains as search engines poorly support it. We introduce Solvent, a
mixed-initiative system where annotators structure abstracts of academic papers
into different aspects and use a semantic model to find analogies among
research papers and across different domains. These results demonstrate a new
path towards computationally supported knowledge sharing in research
communities.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Scientific discoveries are often driven by finding analogies in distant
domains, but the growing number of papers makes it difficult to find relevant
ideas in a single discipline, let alone distant analogies in other domains. To
provide computational support for finding analogies across domains, we
introduce Solvent, a mixed-initiative system where humans annotate aspects of
research papers that denote their background (the high-level problems being
addressed), purpose (the specific problems being addressed), mechanism (how
they achieved their purpose), and findings (what they learned/achieved), and a
computational model constructs a semantic representation from these annotations
that can be used to find analogies among the research papers. We demonstrate
that this system finds more analogies than baseline information-retrieval
approaches; that annotators and annotations can generalize beyond domain; and
that the resulting analogies found are useful to experts. These results
demonstrate a novel path towards computationally supported knowledge sharing in
research communities.</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/solvent.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Solvent', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joel Chan, Joseph Chee Chang, Tom Hope, Dafna Shahaf, Aniket Kittur. 2018.
Solvent: A Mixed Initiative System for Finding Analogies between Research Papers
In Proceedings of the 2018 ACM Human-Computer Interaction: CSCW 2018.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{chan2018solvent,
  title={SOLVENT: A Mixed Initiative System for Finding Analogies between Research Papers},
  author={CHAN, JOEL and CHANG, JOSEPH CHEE and HOPE, TOM and SHAHAF, DAFNA and KITTUR, ANIKET},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2018 ACM Human-Computer Interaction: CSCW},
  series = {CSCW'18},
  year={2018}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evorus]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-evorus/"/>
    <updated>2018-04-21T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-evorus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong><em><i class="fa fa-trophy" aria-hidden="true"></i> BEST PAPER NOMINATION</em></strong>
<br/>
Crowd-powered chatbots are robust than current pure AI approach, but can be
slower and more expensive at runtime. We attempted to combine the two
approaches for high quality, low latency, and low cost.  We introduce Evorus, a
crowd-powered chatbot that automate itself over time by learning to integrate
AI chatbots, reusing responses, and assess response quality. A 5-month-long
public deployment study shows promising results. You can <a href="http://talkingtothecrowd.org/">try talking to Evorus today</a>.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Crowd-powered conversational assistants have been shown to be more robust than
automated systems, but do so at the cost of higher response latency and
monetary costs.  A promising direction is to combine the two approaches for
high quality, low latency, and low cost solutions.  In this paper, we introduce
Evorus, a crowd-powered conversational assistant built to automate itself over
time by i) allowing new chatbots to be easily integrated to automate more
scenarios, ii) reusing prior crowd answers, and iii) learning to automatically
approve response candidates.  Our 5-month-long deployment with 80 participants
and 281 conversations shows that Evorus can automate itself without
compromising conversation quality.  Crowd-AI architectures have long been
proposed as a way to reduce cost and latency for crowd-powered systems; Evorus
demonstrates how automation can be introduced successfully in a deployed
system. Its architecture allows future researchers to make further innovation
on the underlying automated components in the context of a deployed open domain
dialog system.</p>

<h2>Try Evorus on Google Talk</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://talkingtothecrowd.org/" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Demo', 'Evorus', 'Website']);" role="button">TalkingToTheCrowd.org</a></p>

<h2>Overview Video</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3SAG8jP-Q-M?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Media Coverage</h2>

<ul>
<li>WTAE TV News: <a href="http://www.wtae.com/article/chorus-chatbot-carnegie-mellon-university-pittsburgh/16870459">Meet the 'Chorus' chatbot: Unlike Alexa or Siri, it's powered by actual people on the other end</a></li>
<li>Trib Live: <a href="http://triblive.com/business/technology/13275597-74/chatbot-developed-at-carnegie-mellon-uses-humans-to-answer-questions-ais-cant">Chatbot developed at Carnegie Mellon uses humans to answer questions AIs can't</a></li>
<li>EurekaAlert!: <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2018-02/cmu-cwa020618.php">Crowd workers, AI make conversational agents smarter</a></li>
<li>CMU News: <a href="https://www.cs.cmu.edu/news/crowd-workers-ai-make-conversational-agents-smarter">Crowd workers, AI make conversational agents smarter</a></li>
<li>Presstext: <a href="https://www.pressetext.com/#news/20180208014">KI-System "Evorus" wird zunehmend eigenständig</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/evorus.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Evorus', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1801.02668" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Evorus', 'arXiv']);" role="button">arXiv</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Kenneth Huang, Joseph Chee Chang, Jeffrey P. Bigham. 2018.
Evorus: A Crowd-powered Conversational AssistantBuilt to Automate Itself Over Time.
In Proceedings of the 2018 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI '18).
ACM, Montreal, QC, Canada.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Huang:2018:Evorus,
 author = {Huang, Kenneth and Chang, Joseph Chee and Bigham, Jeffrey P.},
 title = {Evorus: A Crowd-powered Conversational AssistantBuilt to Automate Itself Over Time},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2018 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems},
 series = {CHI '18},
 year = {2018},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {Montreal, QC, Canada},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolt]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-revolt/"/>
    <updated>2017-05-06T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-revolt</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Generating comprehensive labeling guidelines for crowdworkers can be
challenging for complex datasets.  Revolt harnesses <em>crowd disagreements</em>
to identify ambiguous concepts in the data and coordinates the crowd to
<em>collaboratively</em> create rich structures for requesters to make posthoc
decisions, removing the need for comprehensive guidelines and
enabling dynamic label boundaries.</p>

<p><span style='color: gray'>Work done during internship at Microsoft Research, Redmond.</span></p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Crowdsourcing provides a scalable and efficient way to construct labeled
datasets for training machine learning systems. However, creating comprehensive
label guidelines for crowdworkers is often prohibitive even for seemingly
simple concepts. Incomplete or ambiguous label guidelines can then result in
differing interpretations of concepts and inconsistent labels. Existing
approaches for improving label quality, such as worker screening or detection
of poor work, are ineffective for this problem and can lead to rejection of
honest work and a missed opportunity to capture rich interpretations about
data. We introduce Revolt, a collaborative approach that brings ideas from
expert annotation workflows to crowd-based labeling. Revolt eliminates the
burden of creating detailed label guidelines by harnessing crowd disagreements
to identify ambiguous concepts and create rich structures (groups of
semantically related items) for post-hoc label decisions. Experiments comparing
Revolt to traditional crowdsourced labeling show that Revolt produces high
quality labels without requiring label guidelines in turn for an increase in
monetary cost. This up front cost, however, is mitigated by Revolt's ability to
produce reusable structures that can accommodate a variety of label boundaries
without requiring new data to be collected. Further comparisons of Revolt's
collaborative and non-collaborative variants show that collaboration reaches
higher label accuracy with lower monetary cost.</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/revolt-crowd-labeling.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Revolt', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=3026044" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Revolt', 'ACM']);" role="button">ACM Digital Library</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/revolt-notes.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Notes', 'Revolt', 'PDF']);" role="button">Technical and Design Notes (draft)</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Saleema Amershi, and Ece Kamar. 2017.
Revolt: Collaborative Crowdsourcing for Labeling Machine Learning Datasets.
In Proceedings of the 2017 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI '17).
ACM, New York, NY, USA, 3180-3191. DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.1145/3025453.3026044
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Chang:2017:Revolt,
 author = {Chang, Joseph Chee and Amershi, Saleema and Kamar, Ece},
 title = {Revolt: Collaborative Crowdsourcing for Labeling Machine Learning Datasets},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2017 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems},
 series = {CHI '17},
 year = {2017},
 url = {http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/3025453.3026044},
 doi = {10.1145/3025453.3026044},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alloy]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-alloy/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-07T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-alloy</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong><em><i class="fa fa-trophy" aria-hidden="true"></i> BEST PAPER NOMINATION</em></strong>
<br/>
<strong><em>HCOMP 2016 INVITED ENCORE TALK</em></strong>
<br/>
Many crowd clustering approaches have difficulties providing global context to
workers in order to generate meaningful categories. Alloy uses a
<em>sample-and-search</em> technique to provide a better understanding of the global
context. It also combines the in-depth semantic knowledge from human
computation and the scalability of machine learning models to create rich
structures from unorganized documents with high quality and efficiency.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Crowdsourced clustering approaches present a promising way to harness deep
semantic knowledge for clustering complex information. However, existing
approaches have difficulties supporting the global context needed for workers
to generate meaningful categories, and are costly because all items require
human judgments. We introduce Alloy, a hybrid approach that combines the
richness of human judgments with the power of machine algorithms. Alloy
supports greater global context through a new <em>sample and search</em>
crowd pattern which changes the crowd's task from classifying a fixed subset of
items to actively sampling and querying the entire dataset.  It also improves
efficiency through a two phase process in which crowds provide examples to help
a machine cluster the head of the distribution, then classify low-confidence
examples in the tail. To accomplish this, Alloy introduces a modular
<em>cast and gather</em> approach which leverages a machine learning backbone
to stitch together different types of judgment tasks.</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/alloy-crowd-clustering.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Alloy', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2858411" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Alloy', 'ACM']);" role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Media Coverage</h2>

<ul>
<li>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette: <a href="http://www.post-gazette.com/business/tech-news/2016/05/11/Crowdsourcing-work-Get-rid-of-the-human-supervisor-CMU/stories/201605100127">Crowdsourcing work? Get rid of the human supervisor</a></li>
<li>Campus Technology: <a href="https://campustechnology.com/articles/2016/05/10/research-project-mixes-humans-and-machines-for-better-crowdsourcing.aspx">Research Project Mixes Humans and Machines for Better Crowdsourcing</a></li>
<li>Neuraoscience News: <a href="http://neurosciencenews.com/human-machine-intelligence-framework-4221/">Crowd Augmented Cognition: Combining Human and Machine Intelligence to Accelerate Learning</a></li>
<li>DZone: <a href="https://dzone.com/articles/researchers-work-on-automated-means-of-managing-th">Research Suggests AI Managers Effective for Crowdsourcing</a></li>
<li>PhysOrg: <a href="https://phys.org/news/2016-05-crowd-augmented-cognition-team-tools-combine.html">Crowd-augmented cognition: Team develops tools that combine human and machine intelligence to accelerate learning</a></li>
<li>TechExplore: <a href="https://techxplore.com/news/2016-05-big-small-pieces-humans-crowdsourced.html">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>Spend Matters: <a href="http://spendmatters.com/2016/06/09/crowdsourcing-and-cognitive-computing-are-you-ready-for-the-future-of-work/">Crowdsourcing and Cognitive Computing: Are You Ready for the Future of Work?</a></li>
<li>Science Daily: <a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/05/160511210628.htm">Crowd-augmented cognition - combine human, machine intelligence to accelerate learning</a></li>
<li>EurekAlert: <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-05/cmu-bti051016.php">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>EurekAlert: <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-05/nsf-cc051116.php">Crowd-augmented cognition</a></li>
<li>NSF News: <a href="https://www.nsf.gov/news/mmg/mmg_disp.jsp?med_id=80586&amp;from=">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>NSF News: <a href="https://www.nsf.gov/news/news_summ.jsp?cntn_id=138580&amp;org=NSF">Crowd-augmented cognition</a></li>
<li>CMU SCS News: <a href="https://www.cmu.edu/news/stories/archives/2016/may/knowledge-accelerator.html">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>CMU HCII News: <a href="https://hcii.cmu.edu/news/2016/hcii-chi-computer-guides-humans-crowdsourced-research">Computer Guides Humans in Crowdsourced Research</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Aniket Kittur, and Nathan Hahn. 2016.
Alloy: Clustering with Crowds and Computation.
In Proceedings of the 2016 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI '16).
ACM, New York, NY, USA, 3180-3191. DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.1145/2858036.2858411
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Chang:2016:ACC:2858036.2858411,
 author = {Chang, Joseph Chee and Kittur, Aniket and Hahn, Nathan},
 title = {Alloy: Clustering with Crowds and Computation},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2016 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems},
 series = {CHI '16},
 year = {2016},
 isbn = {978-1-4503-3362-7},
 location = {Santa Clara, California, USA},
 pages = {3180--3191},
 numpages = {12},
 url = {http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/2858036.2858411},
 doi = {10.1145/2858036.2858411},
 acmid = {2858411},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knowledge Accelorator]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-ka/"/>
    <updated>2016-05-07T07:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-ka</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong><em><i class="fa fa-trophy" aria-hidden="true"></i> BEST PAPER NOMINATION</em></strong>
<br/>
Answering complex questions such as "How do I grow better tomatoes?" often
requires individuals to conduct extensive online research and synthesis. Can we
crowdsource this complex, high context process with 100 crowdworkers conducting
microtasks distributedly? The Knowledge Accelerator uses crowdworkers to
extract and synthesize text clips across web pages into coherent articles
without a centralized coordinator.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Crowdsourcing  offers  a  powerful  new  paradigm  for  onlinework.   However,
real  world  tasks  are  often  interdependent,requiring a big picture view of
the difference pieces involved. Existing  crowdsourcing  approaches  that
support  such  tasks -- ranging from Wikipedia to flash teams -- are
bottleneckedby relying on a small number of individuals to maintain thebig
picture.   In this paper,  we explore the idea that a computational system can
scaffold an emerging interdependent,big picture view entirely through the small
contributions ofindividuals, each of whom sees only a part of the whole.
Toinvestigate the viability, strengths, and weaknesses of this approach we
instantiate the idea in a prototype system for accomplishing  distributed
information  synthesis  and  evaluateits output across a variety of topics.  We
also contribute a setof design patterns that may be informative for other
systemsaimed at supporting big picture thinking in small pieces.</p>

<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/knowledge-accelorator.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'KA', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2858364" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'KA', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Media Coverage</h2>

<ul>
<li>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette: <a href="http://www.post-gazette.com/business/tech-news/2016/05/11/Crowdsourcing-work-Get-rid-of-the-human-supervisor-CMU/stories/201605100127">Crowdsourcing work? Get rid of the human supervisor</a></li>
<li>Campus Technology: <a href="https://campustechnology.com/articles/2016/05/10/research-project-mixes-humans-and-machines-for-better-crowdsourcing.aspx">Research Project Mixes Humans and Machines for Better Crowdsourcing</a></li>
<li>Neuraoscience News: <a href="http://neurosciencenews.com/human-machine-intelligence-framework-4221/">Crowd Augmented Cognition: Combining Human and Machine Intelligence to Accelerate Learning</a></li>
<li>DZone: <a href="https://dzone.com/articles/researchers-work-on-automated-means-of-managing-th">Research Suggests AI Managers Effective for Crowdsourcing</a></li>
<li>PhysOrg: <a href="https://phys.org/news/2016-05-crowd-augmented-cognition-team-tools-combine.html">Crowd-augmented cognition: Team develops tools that combine human and machine intelligence to accelerate learning</a></li>
<li>TechExplore: <a href="https://techxplore.com/news/2016-05-big-small-pieces-humans-crowdsourced.html">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>Spend Matters: <a href="http://spendmatters.com/2016/06/09/crowdsourcing-and-cognitive-computing-are-you-ready-for-the-future-of-work/">Crowdsourcing and Cognitive Computing: Are You Ready for the Future of Work?</a></li>
<li>Science Daily: <a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/05/160511210628.htm">Crowd-augmented cognition - combine human, machine intelligence to accelerate learning</a></li>
<li>EurekAlert: <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-05/cmu-bti051016.php">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>EurekAlert: <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2016-05/nsf-cc051116.php">Crowd-augmented cognition</a></li>
<li>NSF News: <a href="https://www.nsf.gov/news/mmg/mmg_disp.jsp?med_id=80586&amp;from=">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>NSF News: <a href="https://www.nsf.gov/news/news_summ.jsp?cntn_id=138580&amp;org=NSF">Crowd-augmented cognition</a></li>
<li>CMU SCS News: <a href="https://www.cmu.edu/news/stories/archives/2016/may/knowledge-accelerator.html">Big thinking in small pieces: Computer guides humans in crowdsourced research</a></li>
<li>CMU HCII News: <a href="https://hcii.cmu.edu/news/2016/hcii-chi-computer-guides-humans-crowdsourced-research">Computer Guides Humans in Crowdsourced Research</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Nathan Hahn, Joseph Chang, Ji Eun Kim, and Aniket Kittur. 2016.
The Knowledge Accelerator: Big Picture Thinking in Small Pieces.
In Proceedings of the 2016 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI '16).
ACM, New York, NY, USA, 2258-2270. DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.1145/2858036.2858364
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Hahn:2016:KAB:2858036.2858364,
 author = {Hahn, Nathan and Chang, Joseph and Kim, Ji Eun and Kittur, Aniket},
 title = {The Knowledge Accelerator: Big Picture Thinking in Small Pieces},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2016 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems},
 series = {CHI '16},
 year = {2016},
 isbn = {978-1-4503-3362-7},
 location = {Santa Clara, California, USA},
 pages = {2258--2270},
 numpages = {13},
 url = {http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/2858036.2858364},
 doi = {10.1145/2858036.2858364},
 acmid = {2858364},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA},
 keywords = {complex workflow, crowd work, crowdsourcing, design patterns, information synthesis},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
