<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Interaction | Joseph Chee Chang]]></title>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/blog/categories/interaction/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2022-04-11T14:58:33-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://josephcc.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Joseph Chee Chang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[josephcc@cmu.edu]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs.do]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-tabsdo/"/>
    <updated>2021-10-10T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-tabsdo</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The nature of people’s online activities has gone through dramatic changes in
past decades, yet browser interfaces have stayed largely the same since tabs
were introduced nearly 20 years ago. The divide between browser interfaces that
only provide affordances for managing individual tabs and users who manage
their attention at the task level can lead to an "tab overload" problem. We
explored a task-centric tab manager called which enables users to save their
open tabs to manage them with task structures and affordances that better
reflect their mental models. To lower the cost of importing, Tabs.do uses a
neural network in the browser to make suggestions for grouping users' open tabs
by tasks.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>The nature of people’s online activities has gone through dramatic changes in
past decades as significant portions of our productivity and sensemaking tasks
continue to migrate to “the cloud,” yet browser interfaces have stayed
largely the same since tabs were introduced nearly 20 years ago. The divide
between browser interfaces that only provide affordances for managing
individual tabs and users who manage their attention at the task level can lead
to serious adverse effects -- commonly referred to as “tab overload.” This
paper explores the design of a task-centric tab manager called Tabs.do, which
enables users to import and close their open tabs to manage them as tasks.
Users can structure and prioritize their tasks to better reflect their mental
models and resume progress by reopening tasks into open tabs. To lower the cost
of importing, Tabs.do uses machine learning to make intelligent suggestions for
grouping users’ open tabs into task bundles with high precision by exploiting
behavioral and semantic features. Tabs.do bridges the gap between current
browser designs that treat tabs as stacks of independent webpages and users who
manage their workflow and attention at the tasks level. We conducted a field
deployment study where participants used Tabs.do with their real-life tasks and
tabs in the wild and uncovered insights around the costs, benefits, and
limitations of a task-centric approach to tab management.</p>

<h2>30 Seconds Preview (UIST 2021)</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/he--Ly0UQ-4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Presentation (UIST 2021)</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZwbVzDRFbGs" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/tabs.do.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'TabsDo', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Yongsung Kim, Victor Miller, Michael Xieyang Liu, Brad Myers, Aniket Kittur.
Tabs.do: Task-Centric Browser Tab Management.
In Proceedings of the 34th ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium: UIST 2021.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{chang2021tabsdo,
  title={Tabs.do: Task-Centric Browser Tab Management.},
  author={Chang, Joseph Chee and Kim, Yongsung and Miller, Victor and Liu, Michael Xieyang and Myers, Brad and Kittur, Aniket},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 34th ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium},
  series = {UIST'21},
  year={2021}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the Tab Comes Due]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-browser-tabs/"/>
    <updated>2021-05-08T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-browser-tabs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong><em><i class="fa fa-trophy" aria-hidden="true"></i> BEST PAPER NOMINATION</em></strong>
<br/></p>

<p>Tabs have become integral to Web browsing yet have changed little since their
introduction nearly 20 years ago. In contrast, the internet has gone through
dramatic changes and increasingly used to support complex sensemaking tasks.
This paper investigates how tabs today are overloaded with a diverse set of
functionalities and issues users face when managing them. We uncovered
competing pressures pushing for keeping tabs open (ranging from interaction to
emotional costs) versus pushing for closing them (such as limited attention and
resources). We further developed rich design implications for future browser
interfaces.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Tabs have become integral to browsing the Web yet have changed little since
their introduction nearly 20 years ago. In contrast, the internet has gone
through dramatic changes, with users increasingly moving from navigating to
websites to exploring information across many sources to support online
sensemaking. This paper investigates how tabs today are overloaded with a
diverse set of functionalities and issues users face when managing them. We
interviewed ten information workers asking about their tab management
strategies and walk through each open tab on their work computers four times
over two weeks. We uncovered competing pressures pushing for keeping tabs open
(ranging from interaction to emotional costs) versus pushing for closing them
(such as limited attention and resources). We then surveyed 103 participants to
estimate the frequencies of these pressures at scale. Finally, we developed
design implications for future browser interfaces that can better support
managing these pressures</p>

<h2>Presentation (SIGCHI 2021)</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pBjIrX9H-Ns" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/tabs.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'TabHoarders', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3411764.3445585" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'TabHoarders', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Media Coverage</h2>

<ul>
<li>Fast Company: <a href="https://www.fastcompany.com/90635776/the-twisted-psychology-of-browser-tabs-and-why-we-cant-get-rid-of-them">The twisted psychology of browser tabs—and why we can't get rid of them</a></li>
<li>MetroNews UK: <a href="https://metro.co.uk/2021/05/10/suffer-from-tab-overload-scientists-study-why-we-have-so-many-open-14540577/amp/">Suffer from "tab overload"? Scientists study why we have so many open</a></li>
<li>Inc.: <a href="https://www.inc.com/jessica-stillman/productivity-browser-tabs-carnegie-mellon.html">Stressed Out by Your 87 Open Browser Tabs? New Science Offers a Fix</a></li>
<li>HackerNews: <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27095701">When the Tab Comes Due: Challenges in the Cost Structure of Browser Tab Usage</a></li>
<li>HackerNews: <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=27157225">Overcoming tab overload</a></li>
<li>Science Alert: <a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/tab-overload-is-a-common-problem-for-people-browsing-the-internet-survey-finds">We're Getting Buried in Browser Tabs And Scientists Want to Fix It</a></li>
<li>EurekAlert: <a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-05/cmu-oto050721.php">Overcoming tab overload</a></li>
<li>NewsGram: <a href="https://www.newsgram.com/skeema-this-tool-will-assist-you-in-managing-your-browser-tabs-more-effectively/">Skeema: This Tool Will Assist You In Managing Your Browser Tabs More Effectively</a></li>
<li>Sify: <a href="https://www.sify.com/news/this-tool-can-help-you-better-manage-browser-tabs-news-education-vfjl5Ebfaiifc.html">This tool can help you better manage browser tabs</a></li>
<li>Revyuh: <a href="https://www.revyuh.com/news/software/apps/browser-tabs-scientists-find-new-way-to-overcome-fear-of-black-hole-effect/">Browser Tabs: Scientists Find New Way to Overcome Fear of Black Hole Effect</a></li>
<li>Carnegie Mellon University: <a href="https://www.cmu.edu/news/stories/archives/2021/may/overcoming-tab-overload.html">Overcoming Tab Overload</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, Yongsung Kim, Julina Coupland, Bradley
Breneisen, Hannah S Kim, John Hwong, Aniket Kittur. 2021.
When the Tab Comes Due: Challenges in the Cost Structure of Browser Tab Usage.
In Proceedings of the 2021 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI '21).
ACM, New York, NY, USA, 15 pages. DOI: http://dx.doi.org/10.1145/
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Chang:tabs:2021,
 author = {Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan and Kim, Yongsung and Coupland,
 Julina and Breneisen, Bradley and Kim, Hannah S and Hwong, John and Kittur,
 Aniket},
 title = {When the Tab Comes Due: Challenges in the Cost Structure of Browser Tab Usage},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2021 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems},
 series = {CHI '21},
 year = {2021},
 location = {Online},
 numpages = {15},
 url = {http://doi.acm.org/10.1145/3411764.3445585},
 doi = {10.1145/3411764.3445585},
 acmid = {3445585},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {New York, NY, USA},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mesh]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-mesh/"/>
    <updated>2020-10-20T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/UIST-mesh</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Consumers can choose from many different products and base their decisions on
the tens of thousands of online evidence about each of their options.  However,
to synthesize this information into confident decisions can incur high
interaction and cognitive costs. Online information is scattered across
different sources, and evidence such as reviews can be subjective and
conflicting, requiring users to interpret them under their personal context. We
introduce Mesh, which scaffolds users in iteratively building up a better
understanding of both their choices by evaluating evidence gathered across
sources. Lab and field deployment studies found that Mesh significantly reduces
the costs of gathering and evaluating evidence and scaffolds decision-making
through personalized criteria enabling users to gain deeper insights from data
to make confident purchase decisions.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>While there is an enormous amount of information online for making decisions
such as choosing a product, restaurant, or school, it can be costly for users
to synthesize that information into confident decisions. Information for users'
many different criteria needs to be gathered from many different sources into a
structure where they can be compared and contrasted. The usefulness of each
criterion for differentiating potential options can be opaque to users, and
evidence such as reviews may be subjective and conflicting, requiring users to
interpret each under their personal context. We introduce Mesh, which
scaffolds users in iteratively building up a better understanding of both their
criteria and options by evaluating evidence gathered across sources in the
context of consumer decision making. Mesh bridges the gap between decision
support systems that typically have rigid structures and the fluid and dynamic
process of exploratory search, changing the cost structure to provide
increasing payoffs with greater user investment. Our lab and field deployment
studies found evidence that Mesh significantly reduces the costs of
gathering and evaluating evidence and scaffolds decision-making through
personalized criteria enabling users to gain deeper insights from data.</p>

<h2>Video Figure</h2>

<h4>5-minute virtual conference presentation</h4>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LNASh9rq9-I?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h4>3-minute video abstract</h4>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NqriHlTfVhU?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/mesh.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Mesh', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3379337.3415865" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Mesh', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, Aniket Kittur.
Mesh: Scaffolding Comparison Tables for Online Decision Making.
In Proceedings of the 33rd ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium: UIST 2020.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{chang2020mesh,
  title={Mesh: Scaffolding Comparison Tables for Online Decision Making},
  author={Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan, and Kittur, Aniket},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 33rd ACM User Interface Software and Technology Symposium},
  series = {UIST'20},
  year={2020}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[SearchLens]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/IUI-searchlens/"/>
    <updated>2019-03-17T08:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/IUI-searchlens</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Whether figuring out where to eat in an unfamiliar city or deciding which
apartment to live in, reviews and forum posts are often a significant factor in
online decision making. However, making sense of these rich repositories of
diverse opinions can be prohibitively effortful, searchers need to sift through
a large number of reviews to characterize each item based on aspects that they
care about. We introduce a novel system, SearchLens, where searchers build up a
collection of composable and reusable "Lenses" that reflect their different
latent interests. Also, the Lenses allowed the system to generate personalized
interfaces with visual explanations that promote transparency and enable
in-depth exploration.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>Whether figuring out where to eat in an unfamiliar city or deciding which
apartment to live in, consumer generated data (i.e. reviews and forum posts)
are often an important influence in online decision making. To make sense of
these rich repositories of diverse opinions, searchers need to sift through a
large number of reviews to characterize each item based on aspects that they
care about. We introduce a novel system, SearchLens, where searchers build up a
collection of "Lenses" that reflect their different latent interests, and
compose the Lenses to find relevant items across different contexts. Based on
the Lenses, SearchLens generates personalized interfaces with visual
explanations that promotes transparency and enables deeper exploration. While
prior work found searchers may not wish to put in effort specifying their goals
without immediate and sufficient benefits, results from a controlled lab study
suggest that our approach incentivized participants to express their interests
more richly than in a baseline condition, and a field study showed that
participants found benefits in SearchLens while conducting their own tasks.</p>

<h2>Video Figure</h2>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dXcTtHMa2DQ?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/searchlens.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'SearchLens', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a>
<a class="btn btn-default" href="https://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=3302321" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'SearchLens', 'ACM']);"  role="button">ACM Digital Library</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>SearchLens: Composing and Capturing Complex User Interests for Exploratory Search.
Joseph Chee Chang, Nathan Hahn, Adam Perer, Aniket Kittur.
In Proceedings of the 2019 ACM 24th Annual Meeting of the Intelligent User Interfaces: IUI 2019.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@article{chang2019searchlens,
  title={SearchLens: Composing and Capturing Complex User Interests for Exploratory Search},
  author={Chang, Joseph Chee and Hahn, Nathan, and Perer, Adam and Kittur, Aniket},
  booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2019 ACM 24th Annual Meeting of the Intelligent User Interfaces},
  series = {IUI'19},
  year={2019}
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bento Browser]]></title>
    <link href="http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-bento/"/>
    <updated>2018-04-21T08:01:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://josephcc.github.com/CHI-bento</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Complex searches can be overwhelming, leading to lots of opened tabs. This tab overload can
make conducting searches on mobile devices especially difficult where screen
real-estate is limited, and progress can often be interrupted. Rather than
using tabs to manage information, we introduce browsing through scaffolding.
Search result lists serve as mutable workspaces where progress can be suspended
and resumed. BentoBrowser is available for <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/bento-browser/id1101530325?mt=8">download from the iPhone AppStore</a>.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Abstract</h2>

<p>People engaged in complex searches such as planning a vacation or understanding
their medical symptoms are often overwhelmed by opening and managing many tabs.
These challenges are exacerbated as search moves to smartphones and mobile
devices where screen real-estate is limited and tasks are frequently suspended,
resumed, and interleaved. Rather than continue to utilize tab-based browsing
for complex search, we introduce a new way of browsing through a scaffolded
interface. The list of search results serves as a mutable workspace, where a
user can track progress on a specific information query. The search query
serves as a gateway into this workspace, accessed through a task-subtask
hierarchy. We instantiate this in the Bento mobile search system and
investigate its effectiveness in three studies. We find converging evidence
that users were able to make progress on their complex searching tasks with
this structure, and find it more organized and easier to revisit.</p>

<h2>Install Bento Browser</h2>

<p>The version on the AppStore is the third iteration of the version from the CHI 2018 paper.</p>

<p><img src="http://josephcc.github.com/images/projects/bento_screenshots.png" style='width: 100%;'/></p>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/bento-browser/id1101530325?mt=8" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Demo', 'Bento', 'AppStore']);" role="button">iPhone App (AppStore)</a></p>

<h2>Video Demo</h2>

<p>The version in the video is the second iteration of the version from the CHI 2018 paper.</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fm5zK1vm1Q8?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h2>Media Coverage</h2>

<ul>
<li>Tech Explorist: <a href="https://www.techexplorist.com/new-web-browser-easier-search-mobile-devices/13794/">A new web browser makes it easier to search on mobile devices</a></li>
<li>THE Journal: <a href="https://thejournal.com/articles/2018/05/02/carnegie-mellons-bento-browser-organizes-complex-mobile-searches.aspx">New Bento Browser Organizes Complex Mobile Searches</a></li>
<li>Science Daily: <a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/04/180425093747.htm">Bento browser makes it easier to search on mobile devices</a></li>
<li>Prikk: <a href="https://www.prikk.world/en/news/wirtschaft/innovation/bento-erleichtert-websuche-auf-mobilgeraten">"BENTO" ERLEICHTERT WEBSUCHE AUF MOBILGERÄTEN</a></li>
<li>CMU News: <a href="https://www.cmu.edu/news/stories/archives/2018/april/bento-browser.html">Bento Browser Makes it Easier To Search on Mobile Devices</a></li>
<li>CMU HCII: <a href="https://hcii.cmu.edu/news/2018/bento-browser-makes-it-easier-search-mobile-devices">Bento Browser Makes it Easier To Search on Mobile Devices</a></li>
</ul>


<h2>Downloads</h2>

<p><a class="btn btn-default" href="http://josephcc.github.com/images/papers/bento.pdf" target='_blank' onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent', 'Paper', 'Evorus', 'PDF']);" role="button">PDF Download</a></p>

<h2>Citation</h2>

<pre><code>Nathan Hahn, Joseph Chee Chang, Aniket Kittur. 2018.
Bento Browser: Complex Mobile Search Without Tabs.
In Proceedings of the 2018 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI '18).
ACM, Montreal, QC, Canada.
</code></pre>

<h2>Bibtex</h2>

<pre><code>@inproceedings{Hahn:2018:Bento,
 author = {Hahn, Nathan and Chang, Joseph Chee and Kittur, Aniket},
 title = {Bento Browser: Complex Mobile Search Without Tabs.},
 booktitle = {Proceedings of the 2018 CHI Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems},
 series = {CHI '18},
 year = {2018},
 publisher = {ACM},
 address = {Montreal, QC, Canada},
}
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
